blitzcorner.com 2014-02-12

# BlitzCorner Sports Network - Privacy Policy

BlitzCorner ("we") respects the privacy of its visitors and customers ("you") and is committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of personal data we collect. This Privacy Policy applies to our online and offline activities. By visiting our website and/or using our services, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

1.   Information We Collect

BlitzCorner.com and any of its Widgets posted upon partnering sites comprise a sports social media network (the "Network"). The Network is designed to create a community for sports fans, allowing fans to submit content to the Network and share it with the other community members. Users who would like to participate in our community shall create their own profiles within the Network. Creation of these profiles requires providing certain personal information some of which will be shared with other members and visitors within our community in order to allow such users to identify each other and expand their personal network. BlitzCorner members are entitled to edit or remove their profile information at any time.

The information we learn from our visitors and customers helps us personalize and continually improve our services to you. We collect information in the following ways:

 1.1   Information You Give Us. We collect any information you enter on our Network or give us in any other way (via chat, messages posted on our bulletin board, interactive widgets, survey information, telephone calls, emails, online forms, etc.). This information may include identifying information such as name, address, phone number, age, email address and information on services ordered. We may ask you to provide your credit card or other financial account information to enable us to charge your account when you purchase services from us. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of the features in our Network or in the services we provide.

 1.2   Automatic Information. We may collect certain types of information whenever you interact with us. This information may include IP address, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, hardware settings, browser type, system crashes, time and duration of connection, run time information about the state of your virtual machine for example: uptime, CPU, network and disk utilization (R/W), etc. we also collect user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit in order to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor and notify consumers about updates to our Network.

 1.3   Cookies. We may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to keep track of your activities on the Network. We also use them to recognize return visitors, to store visitors' preferences, to track our promotions, serve targeted advertisements on the Network and to customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. You may disable cookies in your browser, however, please note, that this may hinder your use of our Network and the services we provide.

Automatic information collected and information collected through the use of cookies will be considered "Statistic Information".

2.   How We Use Collected Information

 2.1   Internal Purposes. All information collected through the Network is used for internal purposes of improving the services provided by us. Such information may help us to customize your browsing experience, better run your work load and inform you about additional products, services, advertisements or promotions that may be of interest to you.

 2.2   Email. In some instances, with respect to registered users of our Network who have agreed to receive emails, we may use your personal information to contact you via email to deliver promotional or informational materials in which you may find interest, as well as to deliver any updates or newsletters you may register to receive. You may choose to unsubscribe from our email notifications and newsletters at any time by sending us an email to [info@BlitzCorner.com](mailto:info@blitzcorner.com).

 2.3   Financial Information. All financial account information you will be asked to provide is protected during transmission using SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption to prevent it from being intercepted as it is transferred over the Internet. We provide this information only to third parties involved in processing payments for the services we provide and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

 2.4   Sharing Statistic Information. Non-personally identifiable information about the Network's users and Network's activity may among other things, be shared with third party service providers who provide targeted advertisements on the Network. The information collected allows us to analyze how users use the Network and to track user interests, trends and patterns, thus allowing us to deliver more relevant advertisements to users.

 2.5   Data Disassociation. The data collected in connection with the ad serving and ad targeting on our Network does not identify you personally and does not include your personal information, but it may include the IP address of your computer. As described in this policy, we may share your information when we have removed from it any information that personally identifies you.

3.   Disclosure of Collected Information

As we respect your privacy, we will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent, except (i) to our affiliates, subcontractors, service providers and other agents in connection with the provision of services to you; (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities;(iii) to an acquirer of all or part of 10Rank Ltd.'s or BlitzCorner's business activity, in which case such acquirer will be permitted to obtain and use such information subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy,(iv) where we deem it necessary to protect the safety of any third party or to prevent violation of our rights, our Terms and Conditions, or the rights of any third party, including the detection, preventing or otherwise addressing fraud, security or technical issues, or (v) as described in this Privacy Policy, to enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information on our Network, through our widgets, message boards, chats, messages or any other public forum, such information can be accessed by the public and may in turn be used by any member of the publicto send you unsolicited communications.

4.   Third-Party Service Providers

Third-party service providers mayinclude advertisers who target and serve some of the advertisements you see on the pages of our Network, and these providers likewise may use their own cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information from our Network. These service providers may use that information, sometimes in conjunction with similar non-personally identifiable information gathered through other websites, to deliver advertisements on the Network, and on other websites that participate in our service providers' advertising networks, that are tailored to match the perceived interests of consumers. This information also may be used to help measure and research an advertisement's effectiveness, or for other purposes.We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before submitting your personal data.

5.   Links to Other Sites

Our Network contains links to external websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before submitting your personal data.

6.   Information Security

We implement commercially reasonable security measures designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personal information we collect.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by it in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee absolute security. You understand and agree that all information collected through the Network is at your own risk and is subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

7.   Data Integrity

Personal data we collect is relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. We take reasonable steps to ensure that data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

8.   Children's Privacy Statement

This children's privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of 13, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

  * This Network is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 as part of the Network. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13 as part of the Network, we will delete such information from our records as soon as possible.
  * Because we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 via the Network, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
  * We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Network.

9.   Verification

We utilize the self-assessment approach to assure its compliance with this Privacy Policy. We regularly verify that the Privacy Policy is accurate, comprehensive, prominently displayed, completely implemented and in conformity with applicable law and conduct our self-assessment on an annual basis to ensure that all relevant privacy practices are being followed. Appropriate employee training is in place and internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of compliance are in place.

10.   Inquiries or Complaints

If you have a question or complaint about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us at [info@BlitzCorner.com](mailto:info@blitzcorner.com). We will investigate the matter and are committed to resolve any privacy concerns that you may have.

11.   Contact Us

If you would like to contact us regarding the use of your personal information collected in connection with our Network, the types of third parties to whom we disclose such information, ways to limit the use and disclosure of such personal information, or to access and receive a copy of, correct, amend, or delete your personal information collected in connection with our Network that is stored on our systems, please send an email to [info@BlitzCorner.com](mailto:info@blitzcorner.com) detailing your request.

12.   Governing Law

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the state of Israel. You and we agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Israel to resolve any legal matter arising from this Privacy Policy. Notwithstanding, you agree that we shall still be allowed to apply for injunctive remedies (or other equivalent types of urgent legal remedy) in any jurisdiction.

13.   Changes to This Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of our Network will signify agreement to such changes. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy electronically on the Network as actual notice to you. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy.
